It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those
good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who
positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy!
Welcome, everyone.
My name is Von Jiener,
and I'm Vice President
of Creative Bankruptcy
for the Fox TV network,
which, at the time of this writing,
is still a thing that exists.
Just from looking at
your clothes and weight,
I can tell you all watch a lot
of free network television.
Am I right?
Excellent.
You have been selected
to be part of a focus group
that could affect one of America's
most beloved television shows:
Family Guy.
That woman looks exactly like me.
That's your reflection, Peter.
Oh.
I'm beautiful.
As you may or may not care,
Family Guy is in its 17th season.
And since Fox is now owned by Disney,
which will someday be owned by Netflix,
which will someday be owned by Pornhub,
we have decided that Family Guy
is ready for a reboot.
Reboot? I thought they said
it was a couple of tweaks.
Yeah, we're supposed to
trust these idiots?
That woman has her finger up her nose.
That's still your reflection, Peter.
Oh. She's beautiful.
Now, as most unfunny women
will tell you,
women are very funny.
That's why our first reboot
is built around
the very popular Louise.
- It's Lois.
- Whatever. The mom.
This is our time
This is our moment
This is a short song for syndication.
Lois!
Going to work, huh?
Yes, Joe, I'm going to work.
Great! More and more women
are doing that.
Good morning, goddess.
You know, I just want
to say again that you were
totally right last night to bring up
that thing I did wrong 11 years ago.
And please feel free
to bring it up again anytime,
even if we're talking about
something completely unrelated.
Thank you, Peter, I will.
Oh, I-I know you will.
- Morning, Lois.
- Hey, girl.
Oh, hello, gay couple
who's constantly jogging.
What are you up to this morning?
Just adopting and pucker-kissing.
Yeah, we're network TV gay,
so all we can do is adopt children
and pucker-kiss, no tongue stuff.
- Isn't that right, sweetie?
- Mwah!
Well, I'm off to my high-powered job
at a fashion magazine,
greeting card company or winery.
I can't wait to see which.
Oh, yay! It's a winery!
Good morning, Judy Greer.
Morning, Lois.
How was your night last night?
Great. I worked out, made dinner,
a little family time,
and had Peter's ankles
up in the air by 11:00.
God, I admire you.
That's what you're here for, Judy Greer.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Bert wants to see you in his office.
- Oh? What about?
- He didn't say.
But it sounded hashtag serious.
Aw, meeting with the boss.
This is gonna be worse than
finding a spider in the kitchen.
Oh, my God.
Peter, there's a spider in here!
Yeah, I know, genius.
Hi, Lois.
I wanted to let you know
I'm considering you for a big promotion.
Really? That's amazing.
Well, the job's not yours yet.
It's between you and one other person,
Smarmy J. Tie-Straightener the Third.
I hit a gay jogger
on my way to work today.
Sorry I only satisfied you
twice tonight.
I found a pouch of
Big League Chew earlier,
and my jaw is worn out.
You did great, Peter.
Good night, perfect.
Aw, I just don't know what to do
about this thing at work.
I... Are we still talking about that?
I mean, it's fine
if we are, w-we just...
We talked about it before dinner
and-and during dinner and after dinner.
No, you're right. I'll be fine.
Good night, Peter.
Oh.
I just want this promotion so bad.
Okay, so we are talking about it.
You know what? I'll make a vision board.
See my success and be my success.
My testosterone is so low I
could not have thought of that.
Would you like me to put on
our sleep ocean noises
with an occasional
shocking seagull screech?
Yes, thanks. I have a big day tomorrow.
Good night.
Excuse me.
May I have your attention, please?
Now, I know you're all wondering
who is going to get the big promotion,
and I'm proud to announce
that person is Smarmy...
Excuse me, where do I put
this briefcase full of money?
Uh, who are you?
I'm president of Wine and
Paint Night Incorporated.
Lois Griffin just landed my account
through her wit,
charm and professionalism.
Is that so? Well, in that case,
the big promotion goes to Lois Griffin!
What can I say? I love my wife.
Eh, it's my show.
Why shouldn't this be me?
'Cause I'm the funny one.
Not on this show you're not.
Or am I?
Ah, I thought we had one more face.
So, what did you think?
And please keep in mind
that your spontaneous comments
will affect the jobs
of hundreds of people.
Come on, you idiots, don't screw me.
The show is from a woman's perspective,
but it still felt like
it was written by a man.
Okay, well, what if I told you shut up?
Yeah, kind of changes things,
doesn't it?
Anyone else?
I'm sorry, I was scrolling
through the weather
in random cities.
Great! You're taking this
very seriously.
You know what, I don't
really get Family Guy.
What's so hard to get?
You just need to have
grown up in the '80s
but still be a teenager.
So, based on that one episode
featuring Lois,
how many of you would
likely watch a second?
Son of a bitch!
Anything else?
Huh, 76 in Santa Fe right now.
Hey, what's going on in that room?
It's a focus group of Arby's executives
watching us eat.
- Oh!
- No way!
- He ate it!
- People will eat anything!
50 bucks says the fat girl eats
a third Big Beef 'n Cheddar.
Who's on it?
- Okay.
- I'll take that. -You got it.
- Oh, come on, buddy.
- Don't do it.
Here she comes.
All right, kid, take your time.
- Yeah!
- Gross! -Damn it!
Many recent shows have found success
by rebooting themselves as
gritty supernatural teen dramas,
like Teen Wolf or Riverdale,
which are watched by as many
as 6,000 people a year,
so we thought a similar approach
might work for Family Guy.
I'm guessing we're wrong,
but let's find out for sure.
Ooh, ooh...
It's a show for teens
A sexy show for teens
Something's not normal
But what does normal mean
In a world that's on fire?
Hey, Goldman,
great job with sports today.
Thanks, Chris. We're almost ready
for the important sports game.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, Ruth.
Good gender-fluid shower?
Great gender-fluid shower.
Dad, what are you doing here?
Putting my gender fluid in the shower.
Also, I'm the town sheriff,
but you don't find that out till later
because it's not relevant to the story.
Chris, there you are.
Patty, what's wrong?
Why aren't you in bitch class?
It's your sister Meg.
She's... dead.
I have to go.
Wait, where are you going?
I'm gonna go to a club
I'm too young to get into
and listen to a band that's on a label
owned by the same parent company
as the network.
Hey, who left their
gender fluid in the shower?
Sexy rain
Sexy rain.
So, what can I get for you sexy teens?
Um, how's the vegetarian lasagne?
Terrible, even at the best restaurants.
We'll have five of those.
It just doesn't make sense.
Who would want to kill Meg?
Um, can we all be quiet?
We've been asked to nod
our heads while the band plays
the song our parent company
is aggressively marketing.
One of us is Richard Gere's kid
Ooh
One of us is Richard Gere's kid.
I can't even with this.
I'm gonna go get some air
and pebble-up my nipples.
Interior club
Moments later.
You guys, check it out.
Patty just got into
the college for people
with bright futures.
Oh, cool. Is she still gonna
major in "lot to live for"?
Yep. I think she's the one kid
who's gonna get out of this sexy town.
- Patty?!
- I'll be right there.
I just have to drink a product-
placement beverage first.
Peach Coke? Stop.
- Patty!
- Where are you?
Patty, are you out here?
Patty?
Oh, I hope nothing happened
to the most disposable member
of our cast.
Guys, look!
She's dead.
Boy, she... she did stiffen up
those nips, didn't she?
Y'all ready for your lasagnas?
We're in the woods.
Guys, it's time to fire up
our superpowers,
because we're also
lesser-known Marvel characters.
And I'm your neighbor,
who you didn't know
was also a superhero, Captain Pedantic.
Are you here to protect Zac and I?
Zac and me, but yeah.
Now is when you find out
I'm the sheriff.
I'm laying...
on a pinecone.
He means lying on a pinecone.
Now what happens?
Now one of us will become
a breakout movie star
and leave the series,
wrecking it for the rest of us.
Yay, it's me!
- Sir, what did you think?
- Pass.
Okay. And how many of you would watch it
if the girls were wearing
white shirts and black bras?
Peter, did you write
the focus group questions?
What? Course not.
"And if you're impressed by the size of
"Alexander Skarsgard's penis,
that doesn't make you gay, right?"
Answer him!
I know you've been here all day,
but it's not like
you have jobs to go to,
so I'm going to show you
one more reboot idea.
Which Wi-Fi should we be logging onto?
Glendale Galleria Public.
Yeah, that's what I've been trying.
Sometimes networks will cancel a show
only to reboot it
with less-popular characters
from the original, while
the more-popular actors go on
to find greater success in
movies or ugly public divorces.
On which we used to rely
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who
positively can do
All the things that make us
He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy!
Family Guy Again is filmed
before a live studio audience.
I'll get it.
Hello? Oh, hey there, Stewie.
Or should I say, "G'day, mate,"
since you're in Queensland,
Australia, where you moved
with Brian and Meg
after Mom and Dad died?
Oh, married life is pretty good.
No, still no kids,
but I've been practicing
a lot by myself.
Masturbating, yes.
Between you and me, I think
Tricia might be barren.
Uh, Stewie, I better go.
Tricia's giving me that look.
Okay, give my love to Brian and Meg,
and hopefully we can come down
there for the season finale.
No? You're just not gonna be
a part of this at all?
Okay, then. Bye, Stewie.
Chris, I'm standing here
in the living room
because I need to talk to you
about something very important.
Look, we've been through this.
It's my house,
and I want to wear shoes in it.
Chris, I offer you a choice.
You can either continue
wearing shoes in the house
or continue having sex with this
age-defying Eastern physique.
Chris, I'm lying here
listening to you toss and turn,
and wondering if there's
something you'd like to discuss.
I don't know.
It's just, it's been so hard
since Mom and Dad died
and Joe moved in
with all his big band records.
Joe!
Chris, I'm lying here
asking you to kick Joe out of the house.
What? He was my dad's
best friend for 20 years.
I can't do that.
Chris, I offer you a choice.
Luckily, I'm the town windower.
For me, every day is a pane.
Can we please stop this?
Yes?
If I give you back my Diet
Sprite, can I leave?
How did you feel about the show?
- I didn't like it.
- Could you be more specific?
I just don't like the people
or what they're saying or doing.
If you could sum up the show
with one sound,
what would it be?
- "Blech."
- For me, it was more like
the last squirt of
a plastic mustard bottle.
Is that our mustard?
No. I always bring one with me
in case the show is kind of...
- Everybody, shut up!
- Hey, it's that sheriff from The Q.
You people don't like anything.
Well, if you're all so smart,
what do you want to see
in a Family Guy reboot?
Yes, unemployable neck tattoo guy.
It's a Bible verse.
Doesn't matter.
Anything above the Adam's apple
means drugs.
I like Netflix. Could you be Netflix?
Yeah, Netflix is awesome.
Of course it's awesome; it's Netflix.
Look, we're stuck being Fox.
We have to deal with it, okay?
- I watch Fox.
- No, you don't. Nobody does.
Yeah, I like shows
that are binge-worthy.
First of all,
"binge-worthy" is not a word,
it's a marketing tool.
You've been brainwashed, sir. But fine.
We'll make Family Guy binge-worthy.
See? Wasn't that terrible?
All right, we only have the room
till 6:00, so what else?
It's not 6:00 yet! What else?!
Young Sheldon is good.
How about Young Family Guy?
How about I murder your whole family?
- What about BoJack Horseman?
- Hard no.
- You'd get to be a horse.
- Hard yes.
- Normal words, but a horse guy.
- Can we please stop this?
You just asked for specifically that.
It's not 6:00! What else?
- I like that Antiques Roadshow.
- Fine.
And you're saying this is...?
George Washington's poop.
That's correct.
I have some news you might not like.
The poop is only two weeks old.
What? How can you be sure?
Well, for starters,
there's a Skittle in it.
Ah, the general had a sweet tooth, huh?
Um, that was horrible.
Eh, I'm gonna tweeze the Skittle out
and go back in a week.
I like those Netflix stand-up specials.
Great. Matter of fact, we filmed one
back when I was an all-setup-
no-punch-line comedian.
So, any of you out there have a futon?
Yeah, yeah, right?
I Ubered here tonight.
Man, Starbucks.
Facebook, huh?
And how about that new chip
in credit cards?
Anybody ever been to Georgia?
The new iPhone is large.
EDM music.
Boo! You stink!
Yeah! Dane Cook already
did all these halves of jokes.
Hey, hey, this is my job.
I don't go down to Burger King.
That was terrible.
Netflix should make 800 more of those.
All right, what else?
What else you guys want?
I like that thing James Corden does:
- Carpool Karaoke.
- I can do that.
Hi. You having a good night? I did.
Just had a devil's three-way.
You know, me and two guys.
I think that's just gay sex.
Why are you telling me all this?
Isn't this Taxicab Confessions?
No, this is Carpool Karaoke.
We're about to sing an Adele song.
Oh, that's gay.
Pull over by this hot guy
and let me out.
I thought I read you guys
were phasing out gay jokes.
That quote was taken out of context
and widely misunderstood.
All right, what's next, you sheep?
I like the Olympics.
Can you guys be the Olympics?
Well, NBC hogs all the good sports,
so we'll get stuck with the boring ones
that the announcers always
have to keep apologizing for.
Welcome back to pairs diving.
And once again,
we are so sorry for this.
Brian, anything to add?
No, just our deepest
condolences to a bored nation.
And we've got Lois down at the pool.
- Lois, anything?
- No. Guys, just so sorry
that any of this is happening.
I-I mean, even once every four years
seems like just way too much.
And they're up in the air,
and now they're in the water.
What is it again? A splash is bad?
Uh, yeah, I think so.
That's so stupid.
I'm sick of all the voices on your show.
- Can you change them up?
- To who?
I like Jon Benjamin voices.
Can you all be Jon Benjamin voices?
- Hey, Joe.
- Hey, Peter.
- Hey, Quagmire.
- Hey, Cleveland. Giggity.
What can I get for you fellas?
Nobody touches my voice.
I liked all of that.
Um, except for the bartender.
Hey, guys, The Coffee Bean's
Wi-Fi doesn't need a password.
Everyone, the reboot is off.
It turns out
the executive who ordered it
was just a squirrel
who snuck into the office.
- What?
- Yes. But in fairness,
it was the same squirrel who
green-lit Brooklyn Nine-Nine,
the show that challenged the notion
that only attractive people
can be on television.
So, what does that mean?
It means Family Guy
is just fine as it is.
Well, the Family Guy reboot is off.
What other ideas do we have?
Brooklyn Nine-Ten?
It's possible
this guy only has one idea.
You know what, I'm glad, after all that,
they let us keep the show
the way it was.
Well, not exactly the way it was.
Hey, buddy, I brought over
my big band records.
- They wanted more Joe.
Your show should have more Joe Swanson.